amautaspanish.com 2019-03-31

# None

AMAUTA Spanish School takes the protection of your information seriously. We guarantee that your personal data is saved securely according to the according to the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).

Our General Terms and booking conditions apply to all our services. Please read through these conditions and read this privacy policy thoroughly. By visiting our website and using our services you consent to our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the following conditions, please refrain from accessing this website and its pages.

The privacy policy below describes our (online) information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

## YOUR PRIVACY

Trust is important to us. We do everything possible to ensure your personal data is safe. Our data protection declaration applies to all personal data recorded on our website, mobile pages, social media channels, emails/newsletters and at the school. The data collected is handled in good faith and is used for business processing and to improve functions on our website; it is also used for analysis (Google Analytics) or marketing (Facebook).

We use aggregate and _non-personally_ identifying information (such as the URL from which you arrive at our site, the browser you use, the pages you visit) without using any information that would identify you. We will use this _non-identifying_ and aggregate information to better design our website and track the results of marketing and promotional campaigns.

## PERSONAL DATA

 _Personal data_ is data through which you may be identified as a person. When accessing our website, various access data such as the IP address, date and time of access, the name of the files or pages viewed, etc., is saved. Personal data can be collected from the forms of our website (booking, free consultation, offers, catalog ordering, newsletter registration, etc.).

## WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT AND WHAT WE USE IT FOR

The information we collect from you helps us to personalize and improve your experience and services we offer and to communicate with you.

When registering for a Spanish course, you provide us with your name, your nationality, your date of birth, your email, your level of Spanish. We use your email to process your online request and to communicate with you. We use the information about your Spanish level or place you in the correct course. When you book accommodation with AMAUTA, you might send us information about any specific health issues, or allergies. We use this to organize your homestay. When you book volunteer work, we ask you to send us your Curriculum Vitae and a motivation letter; those documents are used to organize your volunteer placement. Finally, our financial administration and accountancy use the information they needed to process payments and for our administration and tax purposes; according to law, we need to keep this information for seven years,

### Contact forms website

On certain pages of our website, you can contact us, make requests, or register to receive brochures or Spanish tests, or, you can opt-in to our newsletter or register for webinars. The types of personal information collected on these pages are first name, last name, email address and by occasion, information about your Spanish level or motivation to learn Spanish. You can always choose not to submit the information requested, understanding that you may be unable to take advantage of some features.

On other pages, you can submit basic information about other individuals. For example, if you want to send a link to a friend about our services, you are asked to submit your friend’s email address.

All of your personal data will be used only for purposes for which you submit them. For example, your friend’s email will only be used to forward him your email recommendation. Nor your email, nor the email of your friend will ever be given to third parties.

We will never use or share the personally identifiable information you provide us online in ways unrelated to the those described in this policy, nor will we share your information with third parties without your permission.

Please be aware that when you click on an advertising banner on our website that takes you to a different website, you begin to interact according to the privacy policy of the other website. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement of any website you visit before providing your personal information.

## COOKIE POLICY

We store certain types of electronic information when you interact with us on our website. These ‘cookies’ allow a web server to transfer data to a device to manage records. To find out more about our use of cookies, please read our Cookie Policy.

We have Functional Cookies (those make our website work), we have Analytical Cookies (for Google Analytics) and Marketing Cookies (e.g. for Facebook).

## HOW SECURE IS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We use industry standard measures to protect all information that is stored on our servers and within our database and computers; we limit access to this information to those employees who need access to perform their job function.

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use and transmission of your information, we have implemented the appropriate physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard and secure the information that we collect from you.

To protect your information, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts all of the information that you input into our form. We also encrypt your password whenever you log on to your AMAUTA account.

## HOW CAN I ACCESS MY PERSONAL INFORMATION?

You have the right to request a copy of the personal information we maintain about you, to make any changes, and to ask that it be deleted. Please direct requests to the addresses listed below, in the section How to Contact Us. Conditions apply (for instance, we need to keep certain information according to law for our administration).

## ABOUT CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

This privacy policy was last modified on May 18th, 2018 according to the new GDPR regulations. If we make any substantial changes, we will post those amendments on our website so that you are always aware of the information we collect, how we use it and how you can access or update your personal information.
